<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Website – Applications</title>
    <link>/docs/machinelearning/models/graph-nn/applications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Applications on My Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="/docs/machinelearning/models/graph-nn/applications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: House-GAN</title>
      <link>/docs/machinelearning/models/graph-nn/applications/gans-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/machinelearning/models/graph-nn/applications/gans-house/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;house-gan&#34;&gt;House-GAN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relational Generative Adversarial Networks for Graph-constrained House Layout Generation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2003.06988.pdf&#34;&gt;Paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nelson Nauata, Kai-Hung Chang, Chin-Yi Cheng, Greg Mori, Yasutaka Furukawa&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This paper proposes a novel &lt;strong&gt;graph-constrained generative adversarial network&lt;/strong&gt;, whose g&lt;strong&gt;enerator and discriminator are built upon relational architecture&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main idea is to encode the constraint into the graph structure of its relational networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have demonstrated the proposed architecture for a new house layout generation problem, whose task is to take an architectural constraint as a graph (i.e., the number and types of rooms with their spatial adjacency) and produce a set of axis-aligned bounding boxes of rooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We measure the quality of generated house layouts with the three metrics: the realism, the diversity, and the compatibility with the input graph constraint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our qualitative and quantitative evaluations over 117,000 real floorplan images demonstrate that the proposed approach outperforms existing methods and baselines. We will publicly share all our code and data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
